-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.com ] ==-
Father ...
They really do exist in this world
They ?.. Who is it you are referring to
..
Twelve evil spirits ... that twelve image
that you don't know
They exist in every corner of the world
So ... what do they do
They exist in the war. disaster. tragedy among various
That why they want to hide it
If they are found. then
People will have faith in God
Ressurection to contact the
Said twelve evil spirits found in South Korea.
I can not contact the South Korea's Zheng Kibum Father.
what are we going to do
Seoul
Successful
Go! We are running out of time!
Hurry!
U-turn
twenty one
Lord. do not abandon us...
twenty two
The adsorption of life exorcism evil spirits freed
The Roman church ceremony
twenty three
According to church law solemn exorcism ceremony 1172
Special retreat ceremony to be hosted by Magic
twenty four
Bishop. Father and Priest combined presence
Deputy offering help priests of the clergy
The presence of evil spirits in vivo enchant people
Twelve image Rosicrucian. according to enchant symptoms.
Species numbers were evil spirits
The Priests
The priest is a gold letter Beide Luo
Zheng Kibum now retired priest in the hospital
Exorcist who was together
When God school everyone says he is a Discovery wooden head
Francisco. he is also particularly well-known.
He Is a very stubborn man
I have this man after ousting
I do not know why they came back early
Complete with the work of his own mind
So that people do not get permission
Report directly to the Vatican..
Enchant that was possessed by the ghost children
Is an ordinary high school girl named Li Yingshen
In this case Exorcismus
In other words need presided Exorcism
In general. are now in the hospital Zheng Kibum priests perform rituals
I. as deputy priest to assist
Gold Father you really made my position very difficult
Beide Luo brothers anyway
You should also ask yourself in the end I should or should not do it
You say is what is meant ah
forty five
Dean. I asked you many times
Every time I say the time and your president say it does not matter
You say what is a nonsense twice
Also if people know the Korean church in the 21st century
Exorcism actually do something
I heard just the people you know
Ah believers in Seoul
A traffic accident went to the hospital after being found to have the phenomenon of demonic possession
You will help her to pray
Do not do some simple psychotherapy on line yet
I have been judged according to the basic conditions of exorcism
I first contacted and enchant those who are diagnosed
First her condition and mental illness in general significantly different
I can always hear strange sound
Father.
what sound?
All sound even outside insect voices can be heard
Here the decisive factor is able to attract the animals enchant
So simple Undead
That is miscellaneous ghost
Most can be resolved through some rituals
If it is not a simple Undead
Few in our country as example
But one of this situation is that some Rosicrucian are looking for twelve image
I know. I know..
It is really a dual personality are still celebrating the birth of Jesus Christ.
But some say such things say what rational or ethical
Even those who have faith in the clergy also
The line in front of say in Bishop
Although I do not know why everyone is so afraid
But now there is the suffering of a child being tortured
Do you want to pretend you do not know?
I know all of your preaching
If such a thing will spread out what impact you should also know it
So my formal objection
You should understand that it's your formal finish will go on
Then press the book that written permission folk doctors and priests and then have a deputy on the line.
Do you have the right priest?
Professor Park Hyun has been true and holy Church Road. said the University Hospital.
Compared to the deputy priest in the exorcism ritual
In fact. said that the deputy priest Fr.
Therefore particularly important
Therefore. the conditions will be much needed
I try to end within a week
A child can do anything special
Liying Shen. Liying Shen. I do not like this.  open the door
Ying Shen!
A few months before the accident. we now ask again
We not very understanding that priest
If exorcism that should Specious heresy to teach or teach
That's not it
Because the case is individual students after school graduation of God we can not tell you
It is owned by Francisco . sort of
Not now tantamount to asking you what to KBS MBC
I hung up the good
How it all went to school here
Has been in the convent now a bit anyway. so come
Deputy exorcism ritual priest came to see it
So I take a look
Because the deputy priest exorcist to translate say so proficient Latin German Chinese
Because if you're going to fight evil spirits you must be brave and open-minded. personality agility
If one must have the courage of people
Also has to withstand the temptation of the evil spirits of wisdom
But also have strength to be able to adhere to long exorcisms strong soul.
Real trouble eh? real trouble
And if listening to now lectures in the hospital Zheng Kibum priest will understand the nature of the ceremony
Like in this case. feed your kid
When you snooze. spirits may be attached to you and this kid.
I'm sorry it came out
Finally. Tiger
Tiger Tiger. then 988.686
To be born from the bottom of the soul of the sensitive temperament
How? but why is this kid
Go slowly feeling your very laborious
I was walking slowly
It must be very angry headmaster Father
I was too absorbed in spiritual prayer do so this semester grades
Inter decade there has been a priest appointed by the Deputy reserved
So the last one became the first of the first. he is a final one
"Matteo Ricci" 10 chapter 16
Seventh grade Jiade
86-year-old case of the tiger right to your birth parents are not registered in advance or postpone it
Ah ofcourse
Ok
How kind of school life
Very good in the Lord's protection
Yes and you can read to grade seven
Oh and I also asked the Lord's blessing on it.
Yes
There is a good news and bad news
Which one you want to hear first?
I wanna hear the good news
The good news is. the Pope is coming to visit our school
So to all sing together in the school in BA
That's Really a good news.
And the bad news is this.
You can quit the choir activities
Why should I?
Zheng Kibum Father Francisco there was gold and retired priests
Is an informal member of the Rosicrucian
From the beginning of last winter there  were a child exorcism
But that child suicide to then now is the state of brain death
Several priests. including myself. are helping the exorcisms
In the convent here as a deputy priest of monks
There is some situation
it Will not let me
In fact. as long as nothing to do on the trip along with Fr.
Associate deputy priest
why me
Do not want to do do not do it our choir practice happiness
I just was competent person
This one
This is Shen Father left some of the information you look
Closed mouth
Holy tongue
There are two addresses before the priests monks live
If there is anything you need to go to it
I heard recently who has not seen it but it should be met with the heir
You go to inquire about what happened
Matai Hao monks you do
who are you
Seminary rector Father let me come
Why did he let you come
I am the priest in gold exorcisms fooled deputy priest
Because the door was open I came
I'm sorry I did not expect that you're eating
What is hieratic
I was vice-priest
Now just to send a callow boy came
I'm not going to 30-year-old small
Zodiac is your brother. then 62-year-old tiger
I am 74 years old
This is a book and notes deputy priests do record
Ah this book and notes
Brother why you suddenly do not do it
Physical condition is not very good
Also home to take care of parents
In the home of the parents how the Well
What are you. why are you doing this to be curious
I am sorry
Hello From now listen what I say
You go there also
Puxiu Shi open the door
We see the side bar
Look out
I saw you sitting there. look out
No priest
This time you may see me
There will be sent to the
I did not
No. no such
I and the meat into anything at all competent
Almost on the line ah
Open the door for it you think I'm kidding
What about the line you also cheer priest bar
To help me once again busy bar
You do not think that poor children do
I let you go
Gold priest where he did wrong yet you go
I'm sorry I'm gone
How the monks
What you really have
There does have that crazy kid over there
Rosicrucian
Gold letters poet to sing God Beide Luo Park Hyun true
Gold Father you pray this kid hurry
Tong Chuan prayer sacramental priest gold
Ying Shen ? awake yet
Ying Shen ? I can not sleep always hear a strange sound
One o'clock
Gold Father ? what sounds
Ying Shen ? What could hear the sound of insects and even the dialogue can be heard between
Gold Father ? This is like cold as Shen Ying
What do you say mental health problems
I was inside watching television
I know their
A brain surgery on the right
But what is inside the pocket
what
This is not a tape recorder it
Oh how this over here
Ying Shen ah itch it
Why your body is always moving around to go
Father you do not touch me
Obviously this has been
I really like you. but why do you always priest so
I do not like
But the pain can not speak
but
escape
Flee
You say something more like. then okay
The Rosicrucian sent to Latin Korean believers accident
And you must say that child-related
God often used in such a way that instead of giving us the opportunity is a good thing
Who
Father Dean
I'm sorry I'll rest
Nightmares of it
Is
What dream
Kill a dog
Ah well it seems you want to come help me
Today is the lunar July 15
Buddhism Ghost Festival. also known as Obon
Chi heaviest day
God is the only day of evil spread merit
Today is the only chance to save the girl
Ah line
It set you on the bus to the subway station
And then later on you never quite found
But how so early departure
Go to the capital to get something there Dean
What are you really handle ah
That one
First Exorcist has been exposed so very dangerous and therefore are generally not exposed by the deputy priest to prepare
Do a lot of homework ah
But Kim priest it
Today is the first time we met it
Yes. a few times on the phone talking about it
Nervous it
What can ah
But very curious
Curious ah
Do you remember the Pope in his inaugural speech last words you
That one
People of reason and wisdom
We Catholic
Is very rational and popular religion
Up to now has been done with superstition and irrationality fight
Struggling to like this today
Because you have to go I will send you to
Not open to let you go you know it
I know
And I do not let you go gold Father busy
Italian bride
Death place
Soul away
November 29 the same day
I am a light of the world
Follow my people
Out of the darkness
Life is
Ying Shen ah
Think about it with prayer digestion method
Sacred Music abandon it
No
Fr.
I really can do well again now alright
cheer
Capital dean and professor Park has contacted
The girl
Did some things not to do
Candid steal it back
In the end is how the
Bishops need to check
Do a little bit and then come back all clear
Now they should stop the person
Hello text of the first hospital I was Cui Zhenhao deputy Festival
Gold Father let me come
Gold Father do
Jin Fanxin Father
Gold Father
Two weeks ago sent me yet that how not to do
Please contact the shipping company
Confirm whether the Korea
God bless
Be sure to get it today
Kim is the priest that we must today
Said there has been made
Fr.
Gold Father
Sorry properly bury him eat a lot of bitter people
I will be so for a reason
Not like that
Zheng Father woke up
It seems also to tomorrow to get to the
I will contact you immediately get the
You wooden head ah Discovery
That is their problem
You say more like it
When I come on the
Not how can I say this is not what
Their side
I do not know I do not know
You are inside a stolen or you can figure it out yourself
Today you are not only told me that he said no way I could have any
enough
Until you get that so far has been in the church pray
So let me say this Why
Hey brats Is it my fault that it
Recent young little patience are not
Please please please
Hey come on what you ask me what's the use
Wait for the next call you
I do this is to hang the phone
In short really serious
Well wonder why it tastes so much
What flavor
Father woke up from Zheng began to rot taste is too great
I know you go to rest
Here I see a read advanced invite you if necessary
Ok
Oh we Fessenden come ah
Do you know how much I miss you
Face lost a lot ah
Is there a problem
Knowing what happened why
Re a lot of it
A lot of weight ah Like several people at the same time a body
Fessenden ah dream last night I feel like I went to heaven
It should be doing back there alone ah
However. where there is a lot of living spider crawling towards me over
Oh spider it
That spider crawling towards me over that smell ah
I thought it was a taste of what the original taste of heaven ah
and then
I quietly move along
The guy suddenly bite my feet
Oh sure hurts ah
I also think it will be painful. but would be more sober
But all of a sudden think of you
Previously not always satisfied with it for me
I say something it hurt you more ah
Fessenden ah today and I will not do to be together
I did not like how long left
You lay it
You do not know me busy
To go
You want to reject it last request your teacher
Do not let go
I want to prevent a mere Undead do great things
Who else but you
Small Brotherhood
Who Where
To the soul perish
And walk in the world of evil and all evil spirits answer me ah ah Fessenden
Keep them went to hell
Who Where
Ah Park Professor
Why look for Professor Park
never mind
what are you doing
Father let me come in gold
Gold Father
I know that things have people bring back
That pig it
Pigs do
Puxiu Shi that pigs do
Yes
Already have feelings
The deputy priest
Chila then will this child diarrhea
Also as long as you open the door. then it will go its own toilet
That one
You first come here
You have to go right instead of Professor Park
Yes
why
Father let me be president
You know you are the first of several to do
Has more than a dozen people came to the
Let's go back
Today. it is not to be with me
Who Where
Answer me ah ah Fessenden
I want to know
Who Where
To prevent you
say something
And you go along with male
who is it
Today I own Qula
So I just went
Principal Father let me go look
This time I will definitely go back again confirmed
No matter what happens
I have not lived this life
Nothingness and false
Wasted all my strength
But my power that my Lord
My compensation is that my God
Bi Isaiah 49 chapter 4
Is your favorite part of the priest does
Really until the last
This is called Francisco monastic monk after the bell when the bell tolled evil woods
Produced in San Francisco directly
This one
But national treasure treasure in Assisi
How can I necessarily need
Hey
Caution body
Know what I mean. right
I respect the Lord my God
Down at your clock
Your salvation from all evil. like mold and the evil born of threats
Protection from evil erosion
I went to good
The moon do not yet seem to rise up ah ah
I'm good at the market
Ok I know immediately
But not dictating own dog
Come
The child's father accepted a settlement after appeal
Do not miss any point and come back all clear
We should stop him ah
Hello there
I Cuizheng Hao. deputy Festival
Yeah tied the pig go outside
Barbecue store to like what you bring pigs
You do not point the conscience
I am sorry
Everyone is naturally right
Why so look what you eat
what
Is occasionally say
Really Young ah Young
Sit down
Who lives where ah
Yongin Suji area
Hometown it
I was born in that house prices should have gone up a lot of oh
Your father's occupation
Is the general faculty mother is the same
They are believers it is not only the mother
Brothers do
There is a sister
Accidents do
That almost
suicide
Is not an accident suffered
What accident ah
Well listen detail
Hey do not want to say that even if the tight corner
9-year-old died when they were bitten by a dog
Bitten by a dog
Oh. this was interesting
Listen to detail
This in the end where the fun
But why are you so sensitive that
Are already a thing of the past
I look at the animals killed were wandering in purgatory you know it
Oh very young age encounter these really pathetic how this can do
I was almost in tears
Suffered misfortune left a son
And the son said to become a priest
One percent chance of entering a seminary
Doing and they do not conform to the difficult thing propped
Of course. this is nothing
After that became a priest
Fool sister can go to heaven. like son
Parents are very much suffering heart
Ouch ouch
Really interesting ah
How it is not that right
You know really more worthy of a priest exorcist
Everyone has a past you are not special
So what is it about your past Father
What special it
what happened
A meat do not know is it does not matter
Drink a glass of it
I never drink alcohol even if the
Why not worship the Puxiu Shi
Very timid and do not take the job
Ah we do not like to say too much ah
Those things with a criminal
When their existence was discovered hiding immediately
Instantly found no other possible escape
Fortunately. if the male body into the woman who is likely to occur
For us it is the equivalent of landing a lucky
So long as he does not like to seize
Yes
Just grab enough
Brother to always come almost forgot what you look like a child
Here it is
This is in response to my right
Attention to the body I know not to worry
Brother I remember you next month production period to see you nephew
As if it lost the original bird
Is already confirmed
Park officials determine searched yet received the lawsuit is the
What it did not say
Said to be nothing to say
Hey
We are now five thousand years to see things
Give me nervous
Command crossing so Pudao Shi
There are good to do your homework before you
Jesus would not let them go out demons into pigs body Ricci book 8 31
I also know
Click here
The top-floor tower housing estates
Pumping a re on the go
How the fear
No exorcism actually fight momentum
From now on we are Longyang underworld
Home owners do not go on to find ways to torture him go
I can figure you only use an auxiliary look on the list will not be found
Do not look and do not answer the prayers on the line as long as
Some firm
To see what it
no
Hey you guys really sensitive person
It can not be sensitive
Really do not want to lose a word
Talk about the characteristics of feed image
Image into a serpentine shape lion scorpion
The exorcism is that enough from China's 1942 war in the
The ultimate goal and extraction stage
The purpose of the ceremony is to say the name of the image if the image is then put into the water yang
Wow you seem to gradually be seen on the go
Hello continue dancing is not allowed to rest
I am sorry
Really ready to quit
Hey you crazy yet where to behold
Hello to dress
Today really is the last time
This is how many times ah really too much
You do not see now a mess of it
Do with witchcraft
Master still some strength
Oh today can toss
The child is in a coma state must be her evil spirits trapped a
Guide the children go to heaven right
So you mean not that kill the child yet
Do not think for a murderer
Now trapped if that is equivalent to preventing the
The tragedy occurred in East Asia
You speak justify it
Now exorcism of female high school students ah female high school students
Do what you do
Fr.
You have come today
Yes ah Today I have come to kill you
This really not sorry uncle
See what yet
Sorry bleeding
Nor is it voodoo snake
Is male body hey how our country male
Daughter come yet to exorcism of
Did she have to do witch witch duties
Yes. ah can only accept their fate
Ceremony ready good I'll go up
This finally come to a decent assistant but too young
Is a young but very rude
What Holy Name Yes
Kai Tak
Who gave you take
I do not want to take because like everyone else
The buy good to
Turn this without finishing a turn
what is this
This is the girl's secretions
Our Father in life is not this one
Turned and turned
This is also a steganography
Males encounter will change much yang
This can be used to cheat him
This is a hard-won Professor Park
Can can
toothpaste
In the nose a little bit Tu
Professor Park Oh. you do not come to work here
I want you to start playing right spirit
I want you to start playing right spirit ouch
Professional terminology is Maerduoluo
Carrion taste enchant those issued
You know what it jumping in hospital
There are ten times suicidal behavior
Actually there Suicide words
Was found trying to escape fishes
Want got into a man's body inside but failed
Please sign
You are not doing it fast preparation
Wow really bright moonlight
There is such a day a year
Hey carefully sprinkle this is the way to save your life
Is
To salt from now. there is more than one meter away from Caesar after preparation ceremony
Ok
To meter welcome Le prayers Korean English Latin order
Yes. I know
And this prayer is a prayer of liberation protection
Is
Deputy priest now start recording
Began to pray
The good Lord will give us the protection of the people
Satan as sinners will not give you the main protection
To tell you the name of the Lord
prayer
Satan has been chasing the same people will go to hell
Amen
Take it out
Now all things start happening here you personally to say
Anyway. he would not believe
Fr.
I am now looks all right
Now it seems alive
Thank you Fr.
Can you help me put this unlock
In order to protect people in the battle
I am a British priest Shen ah
You see I now have a good
Eternal life and God your mother
Doctor to help me untie
Anyone who can stop living this person
Mom and Dad. please help me
This man touched me
Nobody in it
This man stroking me
Please help me
Abi world who command
There are gods in heaven. please bless us
Do not let Satan dominate humanity
To accept the Lord's instructions. please convey our prayers
All the power of the devil to weaken
Expel them
Ghost and Ju curse
Or by being disseminated by the sight of the evil curse
Protect your followers face to face with evil injuries sincerity and strength
Eliminate envy and curses
Please become love and victory
So that you are protecting us
Raise the voice of thanksgiving
My Lord with you
my God
I respect God
Raise your arms chaotic evil
Soul and body protectors
All evil will flee
Make carries jealous and malicious evil and evil burst
Therefore. we are your protection
Raise the voice of thanksgiving
Will be with you not to be afraid
The Lord is my shepherd I shall be with the Lord
And you are my Lord together
Please bless your followers from evil harm
On behalf of the shine of the archangels and saints of all Repentance report
Amen
Damn Bach
I do not let you raped sister-in-law yet
The courage of whistleblowers
The father of lies is the beginning of a murderer
In the name of the Father and the Holy Spirit come to ask you
In the name of the Father and the Holy Spirit asks you
Come
Here we were there
Where the wandering here
We migrated in 2430
When came here
Say it
You these monkeys
Only when reached 3.254.630
In the end want until what time
Say it
In the end like here until what time
Say
In the end what you want until the time
Your presence has been found to stay it will only suffer
You have been found
It will only suffer stay
suffer
pain
He died of famine
war
I have been related to peace with you
Besides looking through history
Has always Amen
In the name of the Father and the Holy Spirit to ask you
Why come here
Intelligent people
listen
Like the outside. like when people do not see it alive
Homo sapiens ants ah
Necro told me
Say it
Why come here
We have to prove that you are a monkey
Homo sapiens humans
Humanity
Who guardian of your biggest guy
You never heard of these human voice falling star
He has overcome the world why would there
He has overcome the world.
Why would there
Are you ignoring me ah
This damn meat caught us
I'll find a safer place
This bitch caught me in
Out guys
Four out
Undead are out to give me fourth holy water and red satin
I will prove
You just monkey only
Now just say the name of this guy would be finished
Ready ending
Ok
Lord of heaven is not going to respond to your filthy stench
In the main heaven ah
Lord save me ah
Now he expelled the darkness coming days
Listening to their voice calling you again
In the name of the living saints
Destroy Undead are
mom
Fr.
Le Ying Holy Archangels meters and the name Seraphim
Le Saint meters to welcome on behalf of archangels and cherubim
Le Saint meters to welcome on behalf of the Archangel and Angel
Le Saint meters to welcome on behalf of the archangel and Thrones
Sober point Jiade
male
do not look
To command you in the name of the Lord
Evil beasts
Exhibit your prototype
Four years later. you will die in prison
I'll gouge your eyes nephew born next month
Francisco
bell
Dig out your sister's womb
Look at me
I do not want to see
What can ah
But still very curious
But what it really Puxiu Shi
Fear it
go back
Look at your arm
Going to rot your arm
Go back to say
Here nothing
There's only a madman
Brother do not go
brother
help me
Brother Brother
Beat It
You're not very good at it
go
How not to go long ah
Forgot to wear shoes
Fled back to only you
I have a debt
Time
I could not go back
Too afraid of dogs biting sister
Because a large
it's not your fault
Because your sister is too small
Animal attack would have passed something larger than themselves
There foul smells sometimes make us despair
You also. and no two animals
But God did not create people like that
Yes
Used to know the old monk said the same thing
Kai Tak
Is here
The more you line up now
I know
Could not sleep forever pestering demon
Ok
Who does not know who will not compensate you
Children of Men
Do not fear them
They say do not be afraid
Even survive being stabbed around Lee
Harsh environments
They say do not be afraid
See their faces and do not tremble
Shen Ying of the priest's breathing normal pulse is also very good very good
I am a doctor ah aunt
Why did
who are you
bad guy
Why do this to my daughter
Incredible here
Please send the police over please
Now stop it
To help us know who their teeth right
Not just in our struggle
No time for direct call out of it
Sucrose and sulfur bar
Have brought
You are no longer a priest Internship
Will you join me to call out the rest of the guys
Is
My lord mercy involvement
Not quickly emerged bold evildoer your prototype
You what it is
342 bridge collapse
5 building collapsed
5680 deaths
6682 birth of the individual category
Main command you in the name of the Holy One answer me
Why do you come here
I hate you
40.275 people do not drink
85938 Black Balloon Explosion
7.284.430 deaths
You will perish
I come marching darkness
Do you want to destroy humanity it
Now go back to your place to go
Say your name
Well
What's your name
I hate you
I Haohen Haohen
Say your name
Marr MELS
Father I will seize his
My Father okay
I will seize his
In the name of the Lord of the command you
Marr MELS come out from here
Sorry Ying Shen
Now confidently
Go to heaven it
Ying Shen ah
Thanks to you. ah
The next step is the most important step a
The pig thrown over fifteen meters of the river
More than one hour. then will be very dangerous
We received a declaration
Seize this person
Is known
I would now like to go first
You come stand here
I will immediately come out of you wait here for a while
I am sorry but I have to go now Fr.
There are killings
what is this
I'm leaving you do not move
Killings occurred killings
Receding
This is what
You have nothing to say
Lets you stop
The road will be very hard
God is willing to bless
Front careful
stop
That person sign the word
Children always been brain dead state
Just go day or Paju Mountain
Please hurry to the nearest Han River Bridge
You should go to the hospital right customer
Please hurry up and get going
Arrived
Father your face
Time has passed. then the last remaining exorcist who would become his host
That you be dangerous
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today